# Imam Abullaisi | UI/UX DESIGNER

Sumedang, Indonesia 45362

+62 821 4148 5699

iabullaisi@gmail.com

abullaisi.com

I am UI/UX Designer with 2 years+ of design experience. I was born in Kuningan, Indonesia on June 11, 1999. I am enthusiastic person and passionate to learn about a new things about design, business, and self-improvement. My hobbies are music, sports, film, travel, and books.

# **EDUCATION**

2017-2018 Zenius Education

**2014–2017** Science (IPA) – SMAN 1 Kamal

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

# UI/UX Designer - Troya Academic Platform

February 2021 - April 2022 - 2 months, Sleman Yogyakarta

- Ideating, brainstorming and iterating the design with PICs such as the stakeholders, Product Manager, & Lead Devs, to validate the design and features and gather feedback.
- Creating design system, and responsive high-fidelity design/clickable prototype.
- Lead the UI/UX intern on a study case project & providing mini-workshops.

# **UI/UX Designer Talent -** *Upwork*

December 2021 - Now

Hired for 6 total jobs, acquired a Rising Talent badge, & reached a \$1k portfolio

# UI Designer Inter, UI/UX Designer Freelance - TeamUp Studio

October 2021 - February 2022 (4 months Internship), February 2022 - Now (Freelance), Sleman Yogyakarta

- Conducting research (competitive audit, defining concept model, user flow, information architecture/ site map, and content hierarchy.
- Ideating, brainstorming and iterating the design with PICs such as the CEO, Project Manager, CTO, Chief Finance & Marketing to validate the design and features and gather feedback.
- Creating low-fidelity design/wireframe and high-fidelity/mockup about the product collaborating with another UI Designer on the team, Front-end Developer, & Back-end Developer.

# **UI/UX Designer -** EXPLOID Studios

August 2021 - September 2021 - 2 months, Remote

- Directly collaborating with the CEO who is also a Front-end Developer to validate the design.
- Research and create a sitemap, wireframe, and UI mockup.

# Freelance Designer - Self-employed

June 2021 - Now

• Designing branding Identity such as a logo, stickers, and social media design for clients.

# Junior Designer - Visualspheres Studio

March 2020 - Jan 2021 - 11 months, Remote

- Help and collaborate with PM, Senior UI/UX Designer, & UX Writer to design Web UI for client needs.
- Conducting competitive research, user flow, and sitemap.
- Designing low-fidelity design/wireframe, high-fidelity/mockup, and handoff to PIC.

# Entrepreneurship/Sales/Reseller - Self-employed

2019 - January 2021 - 2 years, Sumedang

• Gadget trading, videogames account trading, financial instrument trading, dropshipping, and also collaborating with Ngabang.us founder to produce ads.

# **Graphic Design Internship -** Logo Bandung (X-Bargo Studio)

May 2019 - June 2019 - 1 month, Bandung

• Directly collaborated with CEO to design an advertising graphic, video, and landing page.

# **Graphic Designer & Marketing -** various project

Jan 2019 - Apr 2019 - 4 months, Bandung

• Collaborating, designing plus branding a logo, advertising, sticker, and social media design on various UMKM/MSME such as Yumi Corn, BagTic, and Sukadiia Consultant.

# **SKILLS**

# **Industry Knowledge**

- User Interface Design
- User Experience Design
- Graphic Design
- Brand Identity
- Competitive Research
- Heuristic Evaluation

**Tools & Technologies** 

- Figma (Auto Layout, Components, Variants)
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

- Sitemap & IA
- User Flow
- Wireframing
- Prototyping
- Design System

#### Languages

- Indonesian (native)
- English
- Sundanese

# CERTIFICATION

# **Full-Stack Web Designer -** BuildWith Angga

<u>Credential ID: kxNc3YcWLl</u> November 2021, Remote/online

**UI Design Basic -** UX Change (KursusUX.com)

April 2021, Remote/online

**UX Design Process -** *UX Change* (*KursusUX.com*)

April 2021, Remote/online